a lot of men and a lot of women that are
having issues it's not just a howto
problem how do I get out of this how do
I find it's a being being issue what do
I mean by that it's who do I need to be
to find a solution for this problem it's
a very diff it's a very slight variation
I want I'm going to say this again it's
not how do I get out of this issue that
that that that was created because when
I went to the how to I went in from this
from this pain from this anger that I
had from the doctor that gave me this
medicine from from shame for not being
able to have sex with my wife there's
all these things but when I switched it
to who do I need to
be okay from that place I said well who
do I need to be in order to share this
message well I need to be a person that
needs to email the PFS foundation and
say I have a story to share and I want
to be the person running that that was
it there was nothing special about me I
don't have credentials I don't I'm not a
therapist I'm not a counselor I simply
said who I who do I need to be and I
reached
out again who do you need to be to be
one just one% better today than you were
yesterday who do you need to be not how
do I do it because when you get to the
house you start to question yourself I
don't know how to do it but you're being
we can be better
we can do that right now everyone
listening that 1% change by the time
it's something that I learned from my my
uh my daughter is eight years old she
has a Spanish teacher she said if she
learns one Spanish word a day by the end
of the year it's 365 words it compounds
right if you just one if you're just 1%
better a day it compounds by 36 365 days
you will not recognize yourself see most
of the people that I speak to they want
to get 50% better they want to get 60%
better they want to change overnight but
I'm going to tell you right now I wish
it worked that way if I could figure
that out if I had the answer to that or
Dr DeVos we'd be millionaires right now
it just doesn't work that way it doesn't
work like that in my business I would
didn't become a millionaire overnight
then became my relationship wasn't
amazing overnight it takes work and it
takes Grace and it takes patience this
is a long day game folks and in your
game in your journey if you're
waiting to be happy later then you're
doing it in the wrong
order start working on your happiness
right now start working on your
well-being right now and the worst
happens is and I'll give you one last
example before we go is I had a
gentleman that had post fastrite
Syndrome from Europe he had his family
was online they were on their last
resort they didn't know what to do I
asked the parents what's going on with
him he they said he hides in his room
days in and days out he hasn't showered
he hasn't cut his hair he doesn't see
his friends so on on speaker I said uh
to
him I want you to do something I'm not
going to tell you anything about my PFS
journey I said when's the last time you
got a haircut he's like I haven't gotten
a haircut in a about eight months or a
year I don't remember I said go get a
haircut and come back then I'll call
I'll talk to you so he goes I don't know
what this has to do with anything so he
went got a haircut and he called me back
and I said let and then I asked his
parents did you get a haircut and he
saides Amir he got a haircut I said good
I
said when you got your haircut were you
depressed he said yes nothing changed I
said I want you to notice something you
can get a haircut even when you're
depressed I said I'm going to I I'll
share you my secret with PFS once you
get back I want you to go on a walk and
come back he like you're kidding me so
he went on a walk and came back he said
now what I said did you go on a walk he
said yes I said were you depressed he
says yes nothing changed I said I want
you to realize something you can go on a
walk and still be depressed in other
words you can still do the activities
you need to do you can't stop living
life until you get better because at the
end end of the
day listen ladies and gentlemen at the
end of the day we're doing all this
stuff to live a wonderful life but what
a shame it is we're stopping our life
until that gets better to live it like
start cultivating a wonderful life right
now because as you build that muscle of
positivity and
strength it becomes easier to live that
wonderful life and then the worst
happens is in a year you still haven't
had your answer that was me I didn't
have an answer about PFS for for many
years I didn't get resolved for many
years but I started Living a wonderful
life as I was looking for the answers as
I was searching for the answers there
are so many people that call me and say
I can't I I can't even look at my wife
until I feel better like what a
shame what a shame I can't I here I
can't I can't I won't it's imposs
possible
to a week later the
gentleman that said he couldn't get a
haircut that couldn't walk he started
working out I said hey are you serious
you worked out he goes yeah he goes I
felt like crap but I went to the gym and
he got he noticed
something his psychology he realized can
be irrelevant to what he can do in the
world I'm going to say that again not
all the time I'm not saying 100% of the
time there's times where just like what
I said with this you just need a rest
but when you have a moment where you can
do something take that opportunity to do
it he started texting me and saying I
started going out to the bars I started
meeting my friends he got a glimpse he
had just a little bit of light coming in
and he started noticing something he
started going back to life he started
going to the bars again with his friends
he started going out with his family and
he said yeah I still feel depressed
every once in a while but it's starting
to become easier and this isn't his
words because I'm starting to go back
and doing the things I stopped doing and
I realize something how much I was
missing now I haven't spoken to him
since I don't know if he's gotten better
but I hope if you're listening to this
you're still going out with your friends
you're still getting your haircuts
you're still working out and you're
still improving yourself
as you're dealing with whatever issues
you are dealing because at the end of
the day we're all going to have more
issues to deal with and we can either go
on the side of trying to figure that out
for the rest of our lives which is going
to be a game we're going to be playing
for the rest of our lives or becoming 1%
better as we continue that Journey